darlings today I'm going to show you how
to get the fresh natural glamorous look
that I created for the Victoria's Secret
Show first I'm going to show you how to
create the complexion of an angel I'm
going to start by applying my iconic
miracle working magic cream it
transforms tired lackluster skin and it
has won countless awards next I'm going
to gently tap my magic eye rescue all
around the eye area next I'm using my
light Wonder Foundation to create a
dreamy fresh and gellick complexion I'm
buffing it into the skin to give an
airbrushed
juhi camera-ready finish
[Music]
darlinks the magic away any
imperfections I'm using my new magic way
concealer everyone at the show is
obsessed with it it Magic's away
blemishes redness pigmentation and fine
lines this is the magic wand of makeup
the precision sponge applicator hugs the
under-eye contour for seamless
application
[Music]
using my powder and sculpt brush I'm
going to lightly dust the t-zone with my
award-winning airbrush flawless finished
powder I'm using my three and one brow
lift brush up the brows to reveal their
shape now fill in the gaps with my sword
shape brow pencil to finish I'm using
the Victoria's Secret bra whenever I gel
in clear to create the ultimate angel
flutter I'm using my life-changing lash
curlers
they are like Victoria's Secret push-up
bra for the lashes to create the biggest
brightest most sparkling eyes of an
angel I'm using my ex a dries eye
palette I'm going to apply the enlarged
shade to the eyelids focusing on the
crease and the outer V of the eyes for a
dreamy seductive ship
[Music]
it's like a dreamy I filter and I knew
it was perfect for the show I'm using my
eye pencil to elongate the intensify the
eyes I'm tracing along the upper lash
line going up and out about
three-quarters of the way along for an
elongating sultry angel
completely dreamy angel eyes by a prime
bit toy secret major lashes mascara to
the lashes for the ultimate easy contour
i'm going to take my best-selling
award-winning film star bronze & Glow
palette and sculpt in supermodel
cheekbones
next I'm going to use my Hollywood
beauty light wand which is gives you an
instant dreamy glow it's like walking
around with a diva light on your face
I'm applying it to the tops of the
cheekbones down the nose into the
Cupid's bow and chin and into the inner
corners of the eyes for instant
illumination and freshness to create a
seductive supermodel lip I'm going to
reshape and resize the lips of my genius
lip cheat lipliner in supersize me I
[Music]
then applied the Victoria's Secret Show
stopper liquid lip for a pretty pink
palette to finish the look I'm going to
apply my cheap to chic blusher in
ecstacy and finally my famous supermodel
body that I cannot live without
[Music]
so there you have it a gorgeous glowing
Victoria Secret look so you too can cast
the spell
[Music]